Takudzwa R. Mambwere

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Computer science is my degree course of first choice. It has many specialisations and it is growing and evolving at a very high rate. Computers are indispensable and influential tools in our present lives and in the future. They help all kinds of businesses with analysing data and decision making for machines and humans. My desire is to be part of this information technology evolution with a special focus on Software Engineering. I am positive that Sapienza university will afford me the opportunity to study this program, a subject which has been of huge fascination and interest in my high school years.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Family name: Mambwere

First names: Takudzwa Ronald Mambwere

Date of birth: 22 January 2004

Country and city of residence: Johannesburg, South Africa

Nationality: Zimbabwean, Permanent Resident of South Africa Contact: +27 64 979 3776; tamambwere@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Pinnacle College Kyalami

St. Albans College

IVA GLOBAL ONLINE SCHOOL | National Senior Certificate

2018 - 2019

2019 - 2021

2021 - 2022

• 2022 High School Graduate

- Outstanding Achievement x2 (80 -100%)
- Meritorious Achievement x4 (70 79%)
- Top of class in Information Technology

EXPERIENCE

Manager of Senior High Program Organization

January 2023 – Present

IVA GLOBAL ONLINE SCHOOL | Sandton, South Africa

Constructing and arranging a multitude of permutations regarding time class slots for students and staff that pertain to specific educational subjects within different Grades for the course of the 2023 academic year.

Key Accomplishments:

• Significantly increased program organization time from the previous two years.

Manager of Information Technology Support

2023 - Present

IVA GLOBAL ONLINE SCHOOL | Sandton, South Africa

- Front line manager providing technical assistance for a multi-million-dollar online school.
- Providing technical assistance to customers, primarily parents, students and some staff.

SKILLS & INTERESTS/HOBBIES

Java, SQL, Basics of Computational hardware and software, Communication, Digital Marketing

| Football | Tennis | Basketball | Swimming

Signature:	SD	Date:	2023/02/02
- 8 ······			